etilize.com 2014-12-21

# Etilize Privacy Policy

We respect the rights of our customers and website users, your information will never be given to any third-party without consent

## GfK Etilize is committed to respecting the privacy of our users. This Privacy Statement sets forth the online data collection and usage policies and practices that apply to our website. By using our website, you consent to the policies and practices described in this Statement. 

This Privacy Statement applies solely to the information collected on www.etilize.com. 

## In some areas of our Web site, Etilize requests that you provide personal information such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, referral source, and any other information from which your identity is evident. 

We also gather or may gather certain information about your use of our site, such as what areas you visit and which links you access. Moreover, there is information about your computer hardware and software that is or may be collected by Etilize. This information can include without limitation your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses.

## We use the information we gather on our Web site for the purpose of operating and improving the Etilize site, promoting a positive user experience, customer relationship management, business development and lead generation. 

We may also use the information we gather to inform you of other products or services available from Etilize. We may also use it to contact you about your opinion of current products and services or potential new products and services that may be offered. 

We may use your contact information in order to send you e-mail or other communications regarding updates to the Etilize site, such as new Etilize opportunities and resources.

## We do not disclose to third parties your personal information or information about your use of the Etilize Web site (such as the areas you visit or links you click), except as set forth in the following four subparagraphs. 

We may supply your contact information to third parties such as partners, affiliates, data aggregators, or others for the purpose of sending you e-mail or otherwise communicating with you. 

We may disclose such information to companies and individuals we employ to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include hosting our Web servers, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing lead generation, and providing customer service. These companies and individuals will have access to your personal information as necessary to perform their functions, but they may not share that information with any other third party. 

We may disclose such information if legally required to do so, if requested to do so by a governmental entity or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect the rights or property of Etilize or its affiliated companies; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security; or (d) protect the personal safety of users or the public. 

We may disclose and transfer such information to a third party who acquires all or a substantial portion of Etilize's business, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, consolidation or purchase of all or a substantial portion of our assets. In addition, in the event Etilize becomes the subject of a bankruptcy proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, Etilize or its trustee in bankruptcy may sell, license or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the bankruptcy court. 

## Etilize may use "cookies" to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard drive by a Web page server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to your computer, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. 

You may have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline all cookies if you prefer. Alternatively, you may be able to modify your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is tendered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis. If you choose to decline cookies, however, that may hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on the Etilize Web site. 

If you opted to receive newsletters, commercial e-mails or other communications from Etilize but subsequently change your mind, you may opt-out at any time by sending an email to [unsubscribe@etilize.com. ](mailto:unsubscribe@etilize.com)This e-mail address is being protected from spambots. Please type "UNSUBSCRIBE" in the subject header of the email. 

## For more information about how you can opt out of Google's use of cookies, visit the [Ads Preferences Manager](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). You can also opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

## Etilize has implemented reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes.

## If we decide to change our Privacy Statement for www.etilize.com, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it. 

If at any time, you have questions or concerns about Etilize's Privacy Statement, please feel free to email us at [contact_us@etilize.com](mailto:contact_us@etilize.com). Update effective May 15, 2009
